export const ansQuizData = {
  answers: [
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22f9",
      questionText:
        "In order to obtain your commercial driver's license (COL), you must first: ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "Have all restrictions removed from your personal driver'S license ",
        "Be at least 15-years Old ",
        "Get an endorsement for passenger carrying vehicles ",
        "Obtain a commercial learner permit (CLP) ",
      ],
      quesAnswer: "Obtain a commercial learner permit (CLP) ",
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22fa",
      questionText:
        "Which Of the following requires an endorsement on your CDL? ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "Manual transmission  ",
        "using an ELD ",
        "Air brakers ",
        "Double/triple trailers ",
      ],
      quesAnswer: "Air brakers ",
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22fb",
      questionText:
        "According to the FMCSRS, you are qualified to operate a CMV if you: ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "Are currently disqualified from operating a motor vehicle ",
        "Are at least 15-years Old ",
        "Have only one current CDL ",
        "Have passed an IQ test ",
      ],
      quesAnswer: "Have only one current CDL ",
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22fc",
      questionText:
        "Which Of the following is considered a major disqualifying offense? ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "Following the vehicle ahead too closely ",
        "Violating an out-of-service order ",
        "Leaving the scene of an accident ",
        "Texting while driving a CMV ",
      ],
      quesAnswer: "Leaving the scene of an accident ",
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22fd",
      questionText: "Prohibited alcohol use includes which Of the following? ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "Use during the eight hours following an accident, or until undergo a Post-accident test ",
        "Reporting for duty with an alcohol concentration Of 0.01 or greater ",
        "use during the eight hours before performing safety sensitive-functions ",
        "use while cleaning your windows and mirrors ",
      ],
      quesAnswer:
        "Use during the eight hours following an accident, or until undergo a Post-accident test ",
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f2300",
      questionText:
        "The federal size and weight limits apply to a national system of interstates commonly referred to as the: ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "Federal Network ",
        "National Network ",
        "Limit Highway ",
        "Weight Road ",
      ],
      quesAnswer: "National Network ",
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22f8",
      questionText:
        "The Federal Motor Carrier Safety Regulations (FMCSRs) establish basic safety rules and standards for: ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "only motor carriers and CMVs ",
        "all answers are correct",
        "Motor carriers ",
        "Commercial motor vehicles (CMA'S) ",
        "All answers are correct, except tolls ",
        "highway tolls",
        "drivers and Other employees of motor carriers ",
      ],
      quesAnswer: "All answers are correct, except tolls ",
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22fe",
      questionText:
        "Which of the following will result in you being removed from all safety-sensitive functions until you go through a return-to-duty process? ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "Failing an alcohol test ",
        "Testing positive for drugs ",
        "Refusing to take a required alcohol and/or drug test ",
        "All correct",
      ],
      quesAnswer: "All correct",
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22ff",
      questionText:
        "What part Of a combination vehicle is referred to as the 'power unit'? ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: ["Drive axle", "Duals   ", "Tractor ", "Fifth wheel "],
      quesAnswer: "Tractor ",
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22f7",
      questionText:
        "The trucking industry is subject to regulations from which of the following agencies? ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "U.S. Department of (DOI) ",
        "Federal Motor Carrier Safety Administration (FMCSA) ",
        "Bureau of Transportation Statistics (BTS) ",
        "Bureau Of Safety and Environmental Enforcement (BSEE) ",
      ],
      quesAnswer: "Federal Motor Carrier Safety Administration (FMCSA) ",
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
    },
  ],
  questions: [
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22f9",
      questionText:
        "In order to obtain your commercial driver's license (COL), you must first: ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "Have all restrictions removed from your personal driver'S license ",
        "Be at least 15-years Old ",
        "Get an endorsement for passenger carrying vehicles ",
        "Obtain a commercial learner permit (CLP) ",
      ],
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
      selected: "Obtain a commercial learner permit (CLP) ",
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22fa",
      questionText:
        "Which Of the following requires an endorsement on your CDL? ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "Manual transmission  ",
        "using an ELD ",
        "Air brakers ",
        "Double/triple trailers ",
      ],
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
      selected: "Manual transmission  ",
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22fb",
      questionText:
        "According to the FMCSRS, you are qualified to operate a CMV if you: ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "Are currently disqualified from operating a motor vehicle ",
        "Are at least 15-years Old ",
        "Have only one current CDL ",
        "Have passed an IQ test ",
      ],
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
      selected: "Are currently disqualified from operating a motor vehicle ",
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22fc",
      questionText:
        "Which Of the following is considered a major disqualifying offense? ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "Following the vehicle ahead too closely ",
        "Violating an out-of-service order ",
        "Leaving the scene of an accident ",
        "Texting while driving a CMV ",
      ],
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
      selected: "Leaving the scene of an accident ",
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22fd",
      questionText: "Prohibited alcohol use includes which Of the following? ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "Use during the eight hours following an accident, or until undergo a Post-accident test ",
        "Reporting for duty with an alcohol concentration Of 0.01 or greater ",
        "use during the eight hours before performing safety sensitive-functions ",
        "use while cleaning your windows and mirrors ",
      ],
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
      selected:
        "use during the eight hours before performing safety sensitive-functions ",
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f2300",
      questionText:
        "The federal size and weight limits apply to a national system of interstates commonly referred to as the: ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "Federal Network ",
        "National Network ",
        "Limit Highway ",
        "Weight Road ",
      ],
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
      selected: "Federal Network ",
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22f8",
      questionText:
        "The Federal Motor Carrier Safety Regulations (FMCSRs) establish basic safety rules and standards for: ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "only motor carriers and CMVs ",
        "all answers are correct",
        "Motor carriers ",
        "Commercial motor vehicles (CMA'S) ",
        "All answers are correct, except tolls ",
        "highway tolls",
        "drivers and Other employees of motor carriers ",
      ],
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
      selected: "All answers are correct, except tolls ",
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22fe",
      questionText:
        "Which of the following will result in you being removed from all safety-sensitive functions until you go through a return-to-duty process? ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "Failing an alcohol test ",
        "Testing positive for drugs ",
        "Refusing to take a required alcohol and/or drug test ",
        "All correct",
      ],
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
      selected: "Refusing to take a required alcohol and/or drug test ",
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22ff",
      questionText:
        "What part Of a combination vehicle is referred to as the 'power unit'? ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: ["Drive axle", "Duals   ", "Tractor ", "Fifth wheel "],
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
      selected: "Tractor ",
    },
    {
      _id: "63d9542674e77300784f22f7",
      questionText:
        "The trucking industry is subject to regulations from which of the following agencies? ",
      chapterId: 1,
      quesOptions: [
        "U.S. Department of (DOI) ",
        "Federal Motor Carrier Safety Administration (FMCSA) ",
        "Bureau of Transportation Statistics (BTS) ",
        "Bureau Of Safety and Environmental Enforcement (BSEE) ",
      ],
      createAt: "2023-01-31T17:47:15.950Z",
      __v: 0,
      selected: "U.S. Department of (DOI) ",
    },
  ],
};
